<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CoctailCard</string>
    <string name="label_return">Return</string>
    <string name="alcoholic">Alcoholic</string>
    <string name="nonalcoholic">Non-Alcoholic</string>
    <string name="balloon_glass_description">Balloon wine glasses are a type of wine glass, usually used to drink red wines, that are characterized by an almost spherical shape that is much more rounded than other types of wine glass. The shape of the glass itself is what determines whether a glass is a balloon wine glass or not.</string>
    <string name="highball_glass_description">A highball glass is a glass tumbler used to serve ‘tall’ cocktails and other mixed drinks that contain a large proportion of a non-alcoholic mixer, and are poured over ice. It is often used interchangeably with the Collins Glass, although the highball glass is shorter and wider in shape.Examples: Dark ‘N’ Stormy, Bloody Mary, Mojito, gin &amp; tonic.</string>
    <string name="beer_cocktail_glass_description">Weizen glasses are often confused with pilsner glasses, due to their similar shape and size. The main difference between these two styles, is that the Weizen glasses have more curvature to them, especially at the top of the glass. Starting with a strong, narrow base, the glass has a distinctive curve to it as it goes up. This type of beer glass is much taller than a pint glass, and usually holds at least ½ a liter of beer.Another important characteristic, weizen glasses are designed for and primarily used for wheat beers (Weizenbier). The curved lip at the top of the glass helps trap and encourage a thick foam head, allowing for you to appreciate the full aroma and flavor that comes along with wheat beers.However, be wary of the fruit that is usually served on the rim of wheat beers, especially at bars, as the acidity and juice of the fruit could destroy the foam head.</string>
    <string name="beer_mug_description">The beer mug is incredibly robust, easy to use and holds a lot of beer. Common in England, Germany and the United States, this type of beer glass comes in all sizes.The main characteristic of the beer mug is its wide cylindrical shape with a handle on the side. The thick glass walls helps insulate your brew to keep it cool, while the handle helps prevent your hands from inadvertently warming up your beer (or dropping it when you’ve had too many).Sometimes beer mugs will have dimples throughout the glass. While most believe this is merely for decorative purposes, others argue that the dimples help a drinker appreciate the overall color and clarity of their beer.No matter what you believe, there’s no denying the popularity of this beer glass. They’re easy to use, strong enough to toast your friends in a hearty manner, and it holds plenty of beer!</string>
    <string name="brandy_snifter_description">A brandy snifter is a short, wide, stemmed glass used to serve (you guessed it) brandy. It resembles an extraordinarily squat wine glass, with a voluminous bowl and low center of gravity. A snifter can be used for any spirit, really (and a number of cocktails), but it\'s most commonly associated with cognac, other brandies, whiskey, and port or other fortified wines.The brandy snifter is designed with two purposes in mind: evaporation and concentration of aromas. Its wide bowl leaves a large surface area, which allows the volatile, aromatic compounds plenty of room to waft off the spirit. The wide base then narrows into a smaller opening, which concentrates those compounds and prevents them from escaping in all directions (like a coupe glass might).From there, it\'s a simple matter of gently raising the glass to your nose and enjoying the aromas before taking a sip. It\'s a straightforward design, and it adds a nice touch of class to the presentation of your favorite spirit.</string>
    <string name="champagne_glass_description">The flute style is typically the most popular glass shape for Champagne; it looks elegant and features a nice long stem making it easy for the hand; it’s probably the most recognisable. The elongated shape provides a good-sized serving, allowing plenty of Champagne to be held within your bowl and excess bubbles on the initial pour from bottle to glass.The long stem is essential as it allows you to place your hand here rather than on the bowl, thus preventing your wine from warming too quickly and stopping your fingers from marking the glass.</string>
    <string name="cocktail_glass_description">A cocktail glass is a stemmed glass which has a cone-shaped bowl placed upon a stem above a flat base. It is mainly used to serve cocktails. Its form derives from the fact that all cocktails are traditionally served chilled and contain an aromatic element. Thus, the stem allows the drinker to hold the glass without affecting the temperature of the drink, and the wide bowl places the surface of the drink directly under the drinker\'s nose, ensuring that the aromatic element has the desired effectA standard cocktail glass contains 4.5 US fluid ounces.A "martini glass" is actually an incorrect term referring to a cocktail glass, mainly due to the fact that most martini-style cocktails are served in a cocktail glass.</string>
    <string name="coffee_mug_description">A mug is a type of cup typically used for drinking hot drinks, such as coffee, hot chocolate, or tea. Mugs usually have handles and hold a larger amount of fluid than other types of cups. Typically, a mug holds approximately 240–350 ml (8–12 US fl oz; 8.3–12.5 imp fl oz) of liquid.</string>
    <string name="collins_glass_description">A Collins glass is a tall, narrow glass with straight sides typically used for mixed drinks and cocktails. It is named after the Collins cocktail, made with gin, lemon juice, and sugar and traditionally served in this type of glass.It is typically used for cocktails; specifically those served “on the rocks,” meaning over ice. The tall and narrow shape of the Collins glass helps to keep the drink chilled and diluted at a slower rate, as the ice has less surface area in contact with the drink.The glass is also typically used for shaken or stirred drinks and served with ice, such as a Tom Collins or a Gin Fizz. The tall and slender shape of the Collins glass also allows the drink to be easily garnished with fruit or herbs.</string>
    <string name="cordial_glass_description">Cordial glasses small, stemmed glasses generally used to serve after-dinner liqueurs. Alternatively, they may be used to serve drinks at a party, reception or other gathering. The use of fine cordial glasses lends a touch of elegance to any gathering.Cordial glasses are smaller than a typical wine glass, holding approximately one and a half ounces (± 45 ml) and are often (though certainly not always) made with thinner, more delicate glass.Cordial glasses are also (incorrectly) known as pony glasses; a pony glass is not stemmed, despite holding the same amount of liquid, and is more commonly known as a Shot glass.</string>
    <string name="copper_mug_description">This is a special mug to serve Moscow Mule. Enjoy the refreshment of a Moscow Mule year-round, while reminiscing about a long summer lunch on Bouchon’s patio in Yountville or Las Vegas.  Mix up the bistro’s favorite classic cocktail at home with a Bouchon signature copper mug.  All you need to add is your favorite vodka, Fever Tree Ginger Beer and a squeeze of fresh lime.Volume: 16 oz.</string>
    <string name="coupe_glass_description">Also known as the Champagne Coupe or the Champagne saucer, the coupe is a stemmed glass featuring a broad, shallow bowl. As you may have guessed, this glass was originally developed for champagne, however changing tastes have replaced it with the fluted glass as the go-to glass for champagne drinkers. </string>
    <string name="hurricane_glass_description">The hurricane glass is a tall, curved glass that\'s shaped like a hurricane lamp or vase. It\'s typically used to serve the Hurricane cocktail, from which it takes its name, as well as numerous other tropical and tiki cocktails like the Singapore Sling, Piña Colada, and Scorpion. If a recipe calls for a hurricane glass and you don\'t have one on hand, you can always use a highball glass instead.The hurricane glass was likely invented at Pat O\'Brien\'s bar in New Orleans, sometime in the 1940s. It\'s more decorative than functional, and isn\'t necessary for any drink aside its volume (usually about 20 ounces, which can accommodate large frozen drinks) and beachy aesthetic. However, it can be fun to have around for those days you feel like escaping to a tropical island.</string>
    <string name="martini_glass_description">Probably the most recognizable cocktail glass, the martini glass looks stylish when held. It features a "v" shaped bowl design that requires the drink to be sipped, making it perfect for drinks with little or no mixers. You\'ll hear the martini glass often referred to as a cocktail glass, but the traditional cocktail glass is more rounded and slightly smaller.Use a martini glass to serve these strained cocktails: Martini, Cosmopolitan, Sidecar</string>
    <string name="jar_description">A jar is a smooth-sided, round container that\'s often made of glass. Jars are useful for storing food, from rice to tea bags to cookies. A wide-mouth jar made of pottery might hold Oreos, and a small, short jar could contain homemade jam. When you put something in a jar, you jar it.</string>
    <string name="irish_coffee_glass_description">Irish Coffee Glass 24 cl an elegant and differently designed glass with an ear for the famous coffee drink Irish Coffee. This glass from the manufacturer Libbey has a strong stem and is made of glass with a high thickness that insulates well, both by hand and to keep the drink warm. In addition to Irish Coffee, this glass goes well with other hot cocktails, or a delicious latte.Volume: 24 clHeight: 14.6 cmThickness at the edge is about 4.5 mmDishwasher safe!</string>
    <string name="margarita_coupette_glass_description">A coupette cocktail glass that is traditionally used for serving margaritas. Ensures a stunning and luxurious drink presentation. Can also be used for other cocktails including daiquiris, and for serving desserts. Has a volume of 266 ml.</string>
    <string name="mason_jar_description">A Mason jar, also known as a canning jar or fruit jar, is a glass jar used in home canning to preserve food. It was named after American tinsmith John Landis Mason, who patented it in 1858. The jar\'s mouth has a screw thread on its outer perimeter to accept a metal ring or "band".</string>
    <string name="nick_and_nora_glass_description">The glass has a long stem, a high-sided bowl, a narrow mouth, and a moderate capacity (of about 5 US fluid ounces (150 ml)). It is considered a more elegant alternative to the large wide-mouthed martini glasses that were popular in bars in the 1980s.</string>
    <string name="old_fashioned_glass_description">The old-fashioned glass, also known as a rocks glass or lowball glass, is one of the most common cocktail glasses. It derives its name from the Old-Fashioned Cocktail, which is almost served exclusively in old-fashioned glasses.Over the years, the old-fashioned glass has gained immense popularity, in large part because it isn\'t exclusively used for alcoholic drinks—you probably have a few sitting in your cupboard for juice and water.An old-fashioned glass is usually defined as a short, cylindrical tumbler glass with a thick base and straight sides, though many variations exist. It\'s primarily used to serve drinks on the rocks (over ice), but can also be used for certain neat drinks like the Sazerac. Cocktails served in an old-fashioned glass are usually built right in the glass, or strained over fresh ice after stirring or shaking.</string>
    <string name="parfait_glass_description">The Parfait glass is not used much in American bars but it does have its place. Imported from the soda fountain, where this tall, footed, flare–rimmed glass was used for various ice–cream concoctions, it finds bar use for certain fancy drinks, blender drinks and crushed–ice drinks, often with cream or ice cream in them and usually with elaborate garnishes. Sizes vary greatly—there are mini Parfait glasses, in the 2–3 ounce range, that are used mostly for Pousse–Cafés. Larger ones hover around 8 to 12 ounces. </string>
    <string name="pilsner_glass_beer_description">Structurally, pilsner glasses are tall and slim, made of thin glass and tapered in shape (smaller at the bottom and wider at the top). A pilsner\'s tapered shape enables beer bubbles to rise to the top of the glass, while the wide mouth works to capture a beer\'s foamy head for an aromatic experience.</string>
    <string name="pint_glass_description">Pint glasses are a type of glassware usually used to hold beers, ales, and lagers. They are so-named because they usually hold a British pint of liquid. Pint glasses come in many shapes, textures, and designs, and they are a staple of the modern pub or bar.A British or Imperial pint is equal to 1/8 of a gallon, or 568 mL of liquid. In the United States, a pint is equivalent to 16 ounces, or roughly 473 mL. Most pint glasses follow the British measure of a pint, though oversized glasses are also available, and in the United States, many pubs use glasses that hold a US pint — which is just over 80% of the liquid found in an Imperial pint glass.</string>
    <string name="pitcher_description">A pitcher is a large container made of clay. Pitchers are usually round in shape and have a narrow neck and two handles shaped like ears.</string>
    <string name="pousse_cafe_glass_description">This glass has a similar inwards curve to that of a hurricane glass, with a steeper outwards rim and larger, rounded bowl. Often used for drinks containing fruit or ice cream. A narrow glass essentially used for pousse caf s and other layered dessert drinks. It\'s shape increases the ease of layering ingredients.</string>
    <string name="punch_bowl_description">A punch bowl is a large bowl in which drinks, especially punch, are mixed and served.</string>
    <string name="shot_glass_description">A shot glass is a glass originally designed to hold or measure spirits or liquor, which is either imbibed straight from the glass ("a shot") or poured into a cocktail ("a drink"). An alcoholic beverage served in a shot glass and typically consumed quickly, in one gulp, may also be known as a "shooter".</string>
    <string name="whiskey_glass_description">The most common and well-known whiskey glass is called the old-fashioned glass. Another name for this whiskey glass is the lowball glass, the rocks glass, or the whiskey tumbler. These all refer to the classic short, wide brim, and thick base glass often used to serve whiskey.</string>
    <string name="whiskey_sour_glass_description">A sour glass (also known as a delmonico glass) has a rounded cup with a stem specified for sweet, citrus drinks, such as a Whiskey Sour. The stem helps keep a cold drink from the warmth of your hand.</string>
    <string name="white_wine_glass_description">White wine glasses are generally smaller than red wine glasses. This shape preserves floral aromas and helps maintain a cooler temperature. Full-bodied whites like Chardonnay are served in a glass with a bowl that is smaller than a red wine glass but larger than a light-bodied white wine glass.</string>
    <string name="wine_glass_description">A wine glass is a type of glass that is used to drink and taste wine. Most wine glasses are stemware (goblets), i.e., they are composed of three parts: the bowl, stem, and foot.</string>


    <string name="vodka_description">Vodka is a distilled alcohol that is usually clear and lacking a noticeable aroma or taste. Different styles and varieties of distilled vodka come from Russia, Poland and Sweden, but any liquor made from water and agricultural ethanol can be classified as vodka.</string>
    <string name="light_rum_description">Also known as white or clear rum, it is completely colorless. In the United States, this type of rum is sold at around 80 proof (40% ABV). They are aged for one or more years and filtered to remove any coloring. With a milder flavor and lighter body than other rums, this type is often used in cocktail recipes.</string>
    <string name="applejack_description">Applejack is a strong alcoholic drink produced from apples. Popular in the American colonial era, the drink\'s prevalence declined in the 19th and 20th centuries amid competition from other spirits. Applejack is used in several cocktails, including the Jack Rose. It is a type of fruit brandy.</string>
    <string name="gin_description">Gin is a distilled spirit that is made from grain and flavored with botanicals. It is most noted for its pine flavor due to its main ingredient, juniper berries. There are a variety of styles, from the famous London dry gins to modern gins that are less piney and more approachable. Gin is a Dutch creation and the English made it popular worldwide. Today, it\'s made and enjoyed throughout the world; Spain, Belgium, the Netherlands, and the U.K. consume the most gin. It\'s the main ingredient in a classic martini and vital to the iconic gin and tonic, but there are many great cocktail recipes that show off the botanical spirit.</string>
    <string name="dark_rum_description">Dark, black or golden rum starts off as the same clear spirit that makes light rum. However, instead of being filtered and bottled right after being distilled, dark rums are aged first. by aging the rum in charred oak or wooden barrels for a period of time, they end up with a darker color and a bolder flavor.</string>
    <string name="sweet_vermout_description">Sweet vermouth is also known as red vermouth or Italian vermouth thanks to its color and origin. It has a significantly sweeter profile than dry vermouth and can include up to 15 percent sugar. While it is sweet, it\'s not as intense as sweet liqueurs like amaretto.</string>
    <string name="strawberry_schnapps_description">"Schnapps" is a German term for a strong alcoholic drink, flavored with fruit or herbs and spices, either through the distillation process or by mixing ingredients with a neutral spirit. Flavors such as peach, apple, peppermint and cinnamon are especially popular. Bursting with bold strawberry taste, its sweet flavor can\'t be beat in a Margarita or other favorite mixed drinks. Its red color and luscious strawberry flavor complements tart citrus ingredients in your beverages.</string>
    <string name="scotch_description">Scotch is an alcoholic beverage (known as a spirit) created from water and malted barley; although there are businesses that make it with malted wheat or malted rye. They produce Scotches exclusively in Scotland, specifically in Islay, Speyside, Highlands, Campbeltown, and Lowland.  Scotch whisky can add caramelly, nutty, savory, or smoky character to a mixed drink.</string>
    <string name="apricot_brandy_description">Apricot brandy is a common term for the most popular style of apricot liqueurs, although most of these liqueurs are actually made by macerating cherries in neutral spirit (vodka) rather than brandy. Some apricot brandies might also contain brandy or be brandy-based but in most markets, this is not a legal requirement. Apricot brandy is a common ingredient in classic drink recipes. Created before Prohibition, the Charlie Chaplin cocktail pairs it with sloe gin and fresh lemon juice for a fantastic old-fashioned drink.</string>
    <string name="triple_sec_description">Triple sec is the unsung hero in many classic cocktails, including the Margarita. It\'s a sweet, orange-flavored, clear liqueur that brings a citrus punch to the mix, offsetting notes of spice, earthiness, or smoke that the other spirits provide.</string>
    <string name="southern_comfort_description">Southern Comfort is a unique spiced American whiskey flavoured liqueur, a fun spirit to mix with, created in New Orleans by iconic bartender M.W. Heronin 1874. We have been crafting Southern Comfort for over 140 years, so we know it tastes good. The possibilities for drinks with Southern Comfort are endless. You can make traditional cocktails such as a Hurricane or Margarita, or create your own. Just a small amount of this golden drink will add a peachy and citrusy flavor to your drink, making it even better.</string>
    <string name="orange_bitters_description">Orange bitters is a form of bitters, a cocktail flavoring made from such ingredients as the peels of Seville oranges, cardamom, caraway seed, coriander, anise, and burnt sugar in an alcohol base. When drinking bitters neat, it\'s advisable to use them sparingly. Bitters usually contain a high concentration of alcohol and herbs, so mixing them with a sweetener or mixer can really help to dilute their taste. For those who really want to experience their full flavor, it\'s best to try them in small amounts.</string>
    <string name="brandy_description">Brandy is a liquor produced by distilling wine. Brandy generally contains 35–60% alcohol by volume (70–120 US proof) and is typically consumed as an after-dinner digestif. Some brandies are aged in wooden casks. Others are coloured with caramel colouring to imitate the effect of ageing, and some are produced using a combination of ageing and colouring. Varieties of wine brandy can be found across the winemaking world. Among the most renowned are Cognac and Armagnac from south-western France.</string>
    <string name="lemon_vodka_description">Lemon vodka is not only a tasty and refreshing alcoholic drink that will win the hearts of guests, but also a tincture with health properties. Lemon itself is a rich source of vitamin C, which strengthens immunity and soothes many infections. The aroma is sweet and zesty, ceding to a palate of freshly cut lemon and honey flavor with a silky mouthfeel.</string>
    <string name="blended_whiskey_description">Blended whiskey is a type of whiskey made by combining whiskies from different malt and grain distilleries. A blended Scotch is a blended whisky that\'s a combination of a barrel-aged malt whisky (all barley) and some other grain whisky (barley with other grains).</string>
    <string name="dry_vermouth_description">Dry Vermouth is a type of fortified wine that is flavored with a variety of herbs, roots, and spices. It is made by infusing white wine with botanicals such as wormwood, chamomile, sage, coriander, and gentian, and then fortified with brandy to increase its alcohol content. The most popular sweet vermouth cocktails are the Negroni, Americano, and Manhattan. Dry vermouth has a crisp tart flavor, essentially like a dry white wine. It\'s used in martinis, like the Classic Martini and Dirty Martini.</string>
    <string name="amaretto_description">Amaretto is an Italian liqueur made from apricot kernels, which give the liquor a distinctly bitter almond flavor. Its name comes from amaro, the Italian word for “bitter.” Sweeter notes of brown sugar temper the bitterness of the apricot pits. Amaretto liqueur tastes like sweet almond or cherry. It\'s an absolutely delicious taste, and once you\'ve had it you never forget it. You\'ll love this list of some of the best amaretto cocktails, including the classic amaretto sour and many others.</string>
    <string name="tea_description">Tea can lend complexity to a cocktail in a way no other ingredient can. From green, oolong and black tea to chai and other blends, these cocktails use myriad styles to delicious effect. This Isn\'t Goodbye A floral, citrusy mix. Sing Like a Bee Earl Grey meets gin, honey, and citrus. To infuse a spirit with tea, quickly dip the tea bag in hot water, then drop it in a glass jar or measuring cup with 1–2 cups of spirit in it. Taste test it every few minutes if it\'s back tea or every 10–15 minutes if it\'s herbal.</string>
    <string name="champagne_description">Champagne is a well-loved variety of sparkling white wine produced according to specific rules in the Champagne region of ​France. Synonymous with celebration, champagne is typically produced from a few specific varieties of grapes: pinot noir, chardonnay, and pinot meunier. And yet, it mixes so well with spirits, liqueurs, bitters and citrus that bartenders can\'t help but use the sparkling wine in cocktails. Fortunately for the drinking public, that effort has resulted in countless Champagne drinks, from the French 75 to the Kir Royale.</string>
    <string name="coffee_liqueur_description">Coffee liqueur combines two of many people\'s favorite drinks: coffee and alcohol. Plenty of sugar is added to balance out the alcohol\'s sharp taste, usually. While Kahlua is the most well-known and widely sold, it is hardly the only option available. Coffee liqueur can be used in various cocktails, such as a White Russian, Espresso Martini, or even a simple coffee liqueur and vodka. In desserts: Coffee liqueur can be used to make a variety of desserts, such as tiramisu, coffee ice cream, or even a coffee liqueur cake.</string>
    <string name="bourbon_description">Bourbon is America\'s whiskey. By definition, bourbon is at least 51 percent corn, produced in the United States, and has aged for some time in new, charred oak barrels (there is no minimum defined time unless it is labeled Straight Bourbon Whiskey). It doesn\'t, contrary to popular belief, have to be made in Kentucky. What goes well with bourbon: Pretty much anything, but water, coca-cola, soda water, ginger ale, coffee, angostura bitters, cherry, and anything that complements the taste of bourbons like caramel, vanilla, oak, toasted rye, oatmeal, cornbread, cinnamon, and chocolate.</string>
    <string name="tequila_description">tequila, distilled liquor, usually clear in colour and unaged, that is made from the fermented juice of the Mexican agave plant, specifically several varieties of Agave tequilana Weber. Sipping tequila gives your tongue the ability to really uncover the flavor profile of this drink. It allows you to experience the actual taste. When you slow down your drinking like this, you will notice the flavor profile of tequila is actually the honey.</string>
    <string name="aneyo_rum_description">Unlike other golden rums, Añejo is clean, dry and unmistakably mature. Añejo is perfect for traditional rum-based drinks and for those who are ready for a lighter, drier taste. Warm and welcoming, the amber tones of Añejo have a light and woody aroma with just a whisper of chocolate. It is the perfect spirit for mixing delicious cocktails. Simply mix it with ginger ale and pineapple juice. It\'s that easy.</string>
    <string name="bitters_description">Bitters are small bottles of spirits infused with botanicals (herbs and spices) that are used to flavor cocktails. They\'re essential in modern mixology, as they make drinks taste extraordinarily complex with just a few shakes.</string>
    <string name="sugar_description">Why sugar is added to cocktails? The prevailing view is that these sugars potentiate drinking by making the alcohol taste better, particularly for adolescents, overlooking that some central nervous system circuits implicated in alcohol drinking are also sensitive to brain penetrant sugars like glucose.</string>
    <string name="kahlua_description">Kahlua is a coffee liqueur that\'s made in Veracruz, Mexico with rum, sugar, vanilla bean, and coffee. It was invented in 1936 by Pedro Domecq. Contrary to what you might think, there\'s no dairy! Kahlua is dark brown in color and not creamy at all, though many popular drinks that use it add cream.</string>
    <string name="demerara_sugar_description">Demerara sugar is a type of cane sugar with a coarse grain and light tan color. It\'s used as a garnishing sugar in baking to add crunch to the tops of baked goods, and is also popular for sweetening coffee, tea, and other drinks.</string>
    <string name="dubonnet_rouge_description">This Red Vermouth Wine has cherry, mint, and walnut aromas, with notes of lemon zest, cardamom, and toffee. It offers flavors of orange, nuts, chocolate, and coffee and finishes relatively sweet, with lemon and herb notes.</string>
    <string name="watermelon_description">A juicy watermelon puree tastes great with a splash of vodka, fresh lime juice and a hint of simple syrup.</string>
    <string name="lime_juice_description">Limes, which are high in citric acid and low in sugar, have a sour or tart flavor to them. They have the ability to bring balance to strong drinks by cutting through the alcohol. Conversely, in a subtle spirit, lime can be overpowering and so a more subtle use is desired. Does Lime Juice Reduce Alcohol? Lime juice does not reduce alcohol, but it can help to mask the taste of alcohol. As a result of excessive alcohol consumption, the liver can become ill. Lemon juice, when consumed in moderation, can help to alleviate these symptoms.</string>
    <string name="irish_whiskey_description">Irish whiskey is one of the world\'s great styles of whiskey. It\'s most often triple-distilled from unmalted barley that is typically blended with grain whiskey, though there are single malts as well. Made entirely in Ireland, it\'s a favorite worldwide, especially in the U.K. and U.S., due to its exceptional smoothness.</string>
    <string name="apple_brandy_description">Apple brandy is a spirit obtained by the distillation of cider or apple wine. The apples can be classified as table, commercial, or cider apples, but all are suitable for alcohol production (Pischl, 2011). The sugar content of the average quality fruit is between 8% and 12%.  It\'s often used in cocktails as a substitute for whiskey or bourbon, adding depth and complexity.</string>
    <string name="carbonated_water_description">Bartenders know that sparkling water is a key ingredient in a lot of cocktails and having some at the ready is always a good idea. Sparkling water can balance out ingredients, add some fizzy texture, and impart a pleasant since of minerality. One of the best uses for soda water has to be the Mojito cocktail, it really helps the flavours of the other ingredients shine through as nothing else can. A cocktail traditionally made with rum, our fabulous recipe is made with gin, the juniper of which works so well with the fresh mint, lime and juicy berries.</string>
    <string name="cherry_brandy_description">Cherry brandy is a spirit characterised by its cherry aroma and smooth flavour, accompanied by a mild undertone of cherry pits. Wallachia has a long distilling tradition, so it is small wonder that alongside plums, other fruits began being used as well, such as the late-harvest dark cherries typical of the region.</string>
    <string name="creme_de_cacao_description">Creme de cacao is a sweet chocolate liqueur that stars in many classic cocktails! Here\'s more about what it is and how to use it in drinks. It\'s sweet, it\'s chocolaty and it makes some of the best sweet cocktails in the world.</string>
    <string name="grenadine_description">Grenadine is a commonly used nonalcoholic bar syrup characterized by its deep red color. It is a popular cocktail ingredient renowned for its flavor as well as its ability to give a reddish or pink tint to mixed drinks. Grenadine is traditionally made from pomegranate.</string>
    <string name="port_description">Port wine is typically richer, sweeter, heavier, and higher in alcohol content than unfortified wines. This is caused by the addition of distilled grape spirits that fortify the wine, but also halt fermentation before all the sugar is converted to alcohol, and results in a wine that is usually 19% to 20% alcohol.</string>
    <string name="coffee_brandy_description">Allen\'s Coffee Brandy is a coffee-flavoured liqueur popular in New England, especially Maine. Allen\'s Coffee Brandy is prepared and bottled by M.S. Walker, Inc. of Norwood, Massachusetts. The beverage is 60 proof.</string>
    <string name="red_wine_description">You can try mixing your wine with some orange or pineapple juice or some peach or grapefruit slices. Also, it might be the best time to note that you do not have to stick to one fruit at a time. As one would expect, mixing some fruits and fruit juices with wine would give you a fruity concoction.</string>
    <string name="rum_description">Rum is a spirit made from sugarcane molasses or sugarcane juice. The sugarcane is fermented and then distilled. After distillation, the liquid will be clear and typically aged using bourbon casks, wooden casks or stainless steel tanks.</string>
    <string name="grapefruit_juice_description">Cocktail Grapefruits are exceptionally sweet and juicy. They are a delicious cross between Frua Mandarins and Pummelos. Cocktail Grapefruits are much sweeter and less acidic than traditional grapefruits. Cocktail Grapefruits are grown in the Central Valley of California and are hand picked for the best quality.</string>
    <string name="ricard_description">Ricard is a famed pastis (perhaps even the original) with strong liquorice and aniseed flavours. It\'s the very definition of a French classic and the ultimate taste of the Mediterranean. With big notes of green anise, fennel and liquorice root - there\'s a pungent anise on the nose and a ‘rooty’ sweetness of liquorice. The bitter-sweet finish is herbal and slightly menthol-like. Delicious when diluted with very cold water.</string>
    <string name="sherry_description">Sherry is a fortified wine with a long history from Southern Spain. It\'s a high-alcohol wine made using the historic solera system (a barrel aging and blending system) and is produced in a variety of styles, from dry to sweet and light to intense. Most sherry exhibits nutty, dried fruit, and saline flavors.</string>
    <string name="cognac_description">What is Cognac exactly? Cognac is a specific type of brandy produced from distilled white wine. It must be distilled twice, using copper pot stills, and aged in French oak barrels for a minimum of two years. What is a good mix with cognac? For a simple, long drink as an aperitif, cognac can be consumed with tonic or ginger ale. In Rémy Martin VSOP, this brings out notes of fresh fruit, and even licorice. This is how the aperitif is typically enjoyed by the locals in Cognac.</string>
    <string name="sloe_gin_description">Sloe Gin has a rich red colour, which is the result of the steeping process. The result is a smooth liqueur taste with a beautiful balance between sweet and bitter fruit flavours, plus a hint of almonds from the stone of the fruit. Awards for this gin: 2003 Gold – International Wine and Spirits Competition.</string>
    <string name="apple_juice_description">Who knew that apple juice and vodka would be so delicious?! And when you add lemon juice, maple syrup and cinnamon, they\'re even better. They take just 3 minutes to make and will be sure to please everyone.</string>
    <string name="pineapple_juice_description">The tropical nature of pineapple makes it a natural match for rum, and it also pairs particularly well with agave spirits like mezcal and tequila.</string>
    <string name="lemon_juice_description">The combination of different spirits creates a complex flavor profile that is both sweet and sour. The cola gives the cocktail a refreshing fizz, while the lemon juice adds a bright and zesty flavor that perfectly balances out the sweetness of the spirits.</string>
    <string name="sugar_syrup_description">Why do you put sugar syrup in cocktails? How to make your own sugar syrup - TASTE cocktailsIt is primarily used as a substitute for raw sugar and adds rich volume. As we are working with liquids and ice in cocktails, sugar syrups have the advantage of already being dissolved making it easy to mix in to cocktails much faster and smoother than using granulated sugar.</string>
    <string name="milk_description">Alcohol will curdle milk, but it depends on the strength of the alcohol. Put 100 proof vodka into milk and you get curds. Put 60 proof, and you\'ll likely get away with it. Dairy-based alcoholic drinks tend to be low-proof drinks for exactly that reason.</string>
    <string name="strawberries_description">Match it with just about any alcohol: rum, tequila, vodka, and champagne all pair perfectly. Here are all the best strawberry cocktails to maximize berry flavor in your drink! These famous alcoholic drinks range from the icy strawberry daiquiri to the light and delicate strawberry mimosa.</string>
    <string name="chocolate_syrup_description">Chocolate syrup is a sweet, chocolate-flavored condiment. It is often used as a topping or dessert sauce for various desserts, such as ice cream, or mixed with milk to make chocolate milk or blended with milk and ice cream to make a chocolate milkshake.</string>
    <string name="yoghurt_description">“Yogurt makes a great cocktail ingredient because it imparts creaminess and acidity simultaneously, unlike other types of fatty ingredients that tend to lack acid,” says Death &amp; Co. bartender Shannon Tebay Sidle. “It provides a rich, neutral platform for other flavors.”</string>
    <string name="mango_description">There’s nothing quite like the sweet, tropical flavor of mango. As you might expect, this sunny fruit is perfect for adding pizzazz to cocktails! Mango gives a complex, fruity essence to classic cocktails and takes them to a new level. In fact, we’ve got mango variations on three of our favorite classic cocktails!</string>
    <string name="ginger_description">The punchy rhizome gives drinks a fresh, spicy bite, and it pairs with everything from vodka and rum to smoky scotch. The Ginger Smash epitomizes the ingredient\'s friendly nature. The cocktail features a delicious mix of rum, two liqueurs, fresh pineapple, lime juice and, of course, ginger.</string>
    <string name="lime_description">Limes are sour, round, and bright green citrus fruits. There are many species of limes, including the Key lime (Citrus aurantifolia), Persian lime (Citrus latifolia), desert lime (Citrus glauca), and makrut lime (Citrus hystrix).</string>
    <string name="cantaloupe_description">Cantaloupe has orange, tender flesh and a distinctive, sweet taste when ripe. Honeydew has a smooth, pale yellow-green outer skin and light green flesh. It is sweet when ripe with a mild flavor. The melons are eaten in a similar manner and often appear alongside each other in a summertime fruit salad.</string>
    <string name="berries_description">What are muddled berries? Muddling means to press the ingredients against the side of the glass with a muddler. For a refreshing drink with a little fruit, muddled berries seem to fit the bill. There are so many options with berries.</string>
    <string name="grapes_description">Grape: Pairs well with almond, apple, chocolate, citrus (especially lemon), ginger, hazelnut, mint, pear, pecan, raisin, raspberry, rosemary, strawberry, and walnut. The flavor is an obvious companion for brandy and wines of all varietals, though grape cocktails also do well with a rum base.</string>
    <string name="kiwi_description">The combination of fresh kiwi, mint, simple syrup, and vodka creates a flavor profile that is both delicious and satisfying. A sip of the Kiwi Crusher will immediately strike you with the sweet and tangy flavor of the kiwi fruit, followed by the cooling effect of the mint.</string>
    <string name="tomato_juice_description">A Bloody Mary is easy to make from scratch with vodka, tomato juice, and a few other simple ingredients. The spicy, salty, and savory taste of this classic cocktail makes it perfect for brunch or other afternoon gatherings. This spicy condiment has a sharp smell, which can mask the smell of alcohol. Tomato juice is known for its ability to mask the smell of skunk spray. Since it can help eliminate such a vile and overpowering stink, you can be assured that the juice is highly effective at masking alcohol\'s odor.</string>
    <string name="cocoa_powder_description">Compared with natural cocoa powder, alkaline cocoa powder is darker in color with a brownish-red or even black. It has a stronger aroma and a smoother taste. It is also easier to dissolve in water, so it has a wide range of uses. In addition to baking, it is also very suitable to prepare cocoa drinks.</string>
    <string name="chocolate_description">Though a few spirits fall out of these categories, it\'s generally accepted that the six types of distilled spirits are: brandy, gin, rum, tequila, vodka, and whiskey. Each pairs particularly well with chocolate, but the pairings depend on the blend in question.</string>
    <string name="heavy_cream_description">One of the things I love about heavy cream is its versatility. It can be used to add a smooth texture to a drink or to balance out the flavors of more acidic ingredients. It also pairs well with a wide range of spirits, from whiskey to gin to rum.</string>
    <string name="galliano_description">What is Galliano? Galliano L\'Autentico is a bright yellow, sweet herbal Italian liqueur. It\'s made with a blend of 30 herbs, spices and plant extracts, and was invented in Tuscany, Italy since 1896. Its inventor, Arturo Vaccari, named it after Giuseppe Galliano, an Italian officer of the Royal Italian Army. Galliano is sweet with vanilla-anise flavour and subtle citrus and woodsy herbal undernotes. The vanilla top note differentiates Galliano from other anise-flavoured liqueurs such as anisette, ouzo, sambuca, and pastis.</string>
    <string name="peach_vodka_description">A vodka with a smooth taste, with a sophisticated character of peaches. Peach vodka refreshes your drink with a subtle sweetness that helps summer come early and stay late. This peach-flavored vodka mixes perfectly with your favorite cocktails. Along with ripe peach flavors, folks who drink this vodka experience vanilla and orange blossom notes. The complex profile transitions into a clean finish with a smooth mouthfeel for a refreshing sip.</string>
    <string name="ouzo_description">Ouzo is an anise-flavored liquor produced from grape must (the remnants of wine-making). It can only be made in Greece and Cyprus and may include other spices beyond anise. No other beverage is as uniquely Greek or as closely linked to a culture as ouzo is to Greece. The liquor is sweet, silky, and may also taste slightly of other herbs or spices used in its production.</string>
    <string name="coffee_description">Coffee is a beverage brewed from the roasted and ground seeds of the tropical evergreen coffee plant. Coffee is one of the three most popular beverages in the world (alongside water and tea), and it is one of the most profitable international commodities. It is used also with alcohol as Whiskey coffee or Irish coffee. Whiskey coffee is most often known as Irish coffee. Though many people claim to be the first to create Irish coffee, it is most credited to Joe Sheridan, who found it in winter 1943 in Ireland.</string>
    <string name="spiced_rum_description">A Spiced Rum is any kind of rum that has been flavored with natural herbs and spices. The spices are generally derived from seeds, roots, dried fruits, barks, or leaves. For instance, clove, cinnamon, cassia, vanilla, star anise, citrus fruit, nutmeg, cardamom, orange peel, ginger, pepper, allspice, among many others. The flavor profile of spiced rum can vary widely depending on the spices used and the aging process, making it a popular choice for rum enthusiasts who enjoy experimenting with different flavor combinations.</string>
    <string name="water_description">Water is indeed a useful flavor enhancer, exactly because it dilutes other ingredients and can change their balance for the better. It\'s no secret that the alcohol in drinks can get in the way of our enjoying their flavors.</string>
    <string name="espresso_description">Whether it\'s a warming cup of hot coffee, a quick shot of espresso, or an iced coffee drink, some distilled spirits work better with coffee than others. When you want to spike your coffee, dark liquors like brandy and whiskey, and sweet nutty or creamy liqueurs are among the best choices.</string>
    <string name="angelica_root_description">What is angelica root used for? The roots and fruits yield angelica oil used to flavour liqueurs and in perfumery, while the tender shoots are used in making certain kinds of aromatic sweetmeats. Tea made from the roots and leaves is a traditional medicine for respiratory ailments.</string>
    <string name="orange_description">Love the bright and beautiful citrus flavor of an orange! Turns out OJ is a top notch mixer for cocktails. It can stand in with almost any liquor, though it\'s best known for pairing with vodka. But mix it with champagne to make a mimosa, or tequila to make a tequila sunrise or spin on the margarita!</string>
    <string name="cranberries_description">Cranberry juice adds a great sweet and tart flavor and bright red color to drinks.</string>
    <string name="johnie_walker_description">Johnnie Walker is a popular brand, and Johnnie Walker Black Label is a fun blended scotch whisky to experiment with if you\'re new to the world of scotch. This scotch is made with premium Scottish grains and has an excellent flavor balance.</string>
    <string name="apple_cider_description">Many alcohols mix well with apple cider. Dark liquors like bourbon or dark rum are traditional, but they are by no means the only option. Vodka pairs well with apple cider and is a good light option. You can even let guests each pick their own.</string>
    <string name="everclear_description">Everclear is a brand name of rectified spirit (also known as grain alcohol and neutral spirit) produced by the American company Luxco (formerly known as the David Sherman Corporation). It is made from grain and is bottled at 60%, 75.5%, 94.5% and 95% alcohol by volume (120, 151, 189, and 190 U.S. proof respectively). Everclear is more or like tasting rubbing alcohol. It contains no flavor whatsoever. When undiluted, it tastes hotter and more peppery due to a higher percentage of alcohol. Because of its coarse nature, it has no similarity in taste with other food products.</string>
    <string name="cranberry_juice_description">Cranberry juice is a dark red fruit juice made from cranberries and sugar. This juice is liquid crushed from cranberries, which are acidic berries that grow on small shrubs or vines. Pure cranberry juice is very tart and so is often diluted with other types of juice, such as orange or apple.</string>
    <string name="egg_yolk_description">Adding a raw egg yolk into the mix can help emulsify the other ingredients in your cocktail, says Serious Eats. Plus, whereas egg whites give cocktails a tasteless frothy textural component, yolks add a rich eggnog-like flavor. Egg yolk is the key ingredient in any variation of a Flip cocktail (per Casual Mixologist)</string>
    <string name="egg_description">Egg whites add a foam texture, mouthfeel and volume to a cocktail,” says Sergio Leanza, the owner of and a bartender at Funkidory in London. “They soften the edge of sour drinks and make them feel lighter, and they also make drinks look great.</string>
    <string name="grape_juice_description">Preliminary research suggests that red and purple grape juice, like red wine, may improve cardiovascular health in some ways. To make an alcoholic beverage out of fruit juice, combine vodka, gin, rum, tequila, or whiskey. Adding a liqueur to the drink would also help to sweeten it.</string>
    <string name="peach_nectar_description">Peach nectar is just a juice made with the pulp of the peach included, and it usually has a bit of sugar and lemon juice thrown in for flavor. You can drink peach nectar on its own or add it to other drinks and dishes for extra flavor.</string>
    <string name="lemon_description">Many traditional cocktails call for the versatile and important ingredient lemon juice. Any beverage can be improved and given a zesty twist thanks to its bright acidity and refreshing flavor.</string>
    <string name="firewater_description">Firewater is a mixture of Canadian whisky blended with natural cinnamon flavour and sweeteners. So it is technically not a whisky but probably closer to a whisky-based liquor. It is bottled at 33 % ABV and produced by the Sazerac Company who also makes Buffalo Trace and WL Weller Bourbon.</string>
    <string name="lemonade_description">The most popular liquor to mix with lemonade are gin, vodka and bourbon. This recipe uses the classic vodka, but adds some intrigue with a special ingredient.</string>
    <string name="lager_description">The term lager is used to denote beer produced from bottom-fermenting yeast. Lagers are distinguished from ales, or top-fermented British types of beer. Bottom-fermented lagers have their origins in continental Europe.</string>
    <string name="whiskey_description">Whiskey cocktails are often made with rye whiskey. These cocktails tend to be high in alcohol content and have a bold flavor. If you are looking for a cocktail that will pack a punch, then a whiskey-based drink is the way to go. Some popular whiskey cocktails include the Old Fashioned, Manhattan, and Sazerac.</string>
    <string name="absolut_citron_description">Absolut Citron vodka has provided a kick of lemon flavor and a smooth finish to your favorite cocktail recipes for nearly 30 years. Experience a delightful splash of citrus with the perfect balance between tangy lemon and vibrant lime notes achieved in Absolut Citron.</string>
    <string name="pisco_description">Pisco is technically and unaged brandy obtained from the distillation of recently fermented Peruvian grape musts and juices. Some say its like Grappa because both are made from grapes. Peruvian pisco is especially unique because, unlike other brandies, it is distilled only once. Furthermore, no water is added after distillation, which means you have one chance to achieve perfection with each batch. All other brandies are distilled twice and water is then added to reach a desired proof.</string>
    <string name="irish_cream_description">Irish cream is a rich liqueur made with Irish whiskey and cream. It can be served straight, on the rocks, or mixed into cocktails. You can also use it as an ingredient in boozy, decadent desserts. Many argue that its richness and warm notes of honey and vanilla are unrivaled by any other cream liqueur available. While the exact recipe is a well-kept secret, we do know that Baileys opts for cocoa extract, sugar and herbs as the main other ingredients alongside the whiskey and cream.</string>
    <string name="ale_description">Ale is a type of beer brewed using a warm fermentation method, resulting in a sweet, full-bodied and fruity taste. Historically, the term referred to a drink brewed without hops. A glass of real ale from an English pub.</string>
    <string name="chocolate_liquer_description">Chocolate liquor is a paste produced from ground cocoa nibs from the beans of the cocoa tree (Theobroma cacao). When cooled and solidified, it is used to make chocolate for baking, confections and other applications. It\'s composed of a combination of cocoa solids and cocoa butter, typically at a 50:50 ratio.</string>
    <string name="midori_melon_liqueur_description">Midori (ミドリ) is a sweet, bright green-colored liqueur made by Suntory, flavored with Yubari and muskmelon. It is manufactured in Japan, the United States, Mexico, and France. It was first released in 1964 under the name "Hermes Melon Liqueur", but changed its name to "Midori" in 1978.</string>
    <string name="sambuca_description">Sambuca is produced by the infusion of elder bush and licorice, sweetened with sugar and enhanced with a secret combination of herbs and spices. Tasting Notes: Romana Sambuca is a distinctive, flavorful and unique Italian liqueur. At 42% alcohol by volume, with a bold yet pleasingly sweet anise flavor.</string>
    <string name="cider_description">Cider (cyder, United States: hard cider) is an alcoholic beverage produced by the fermentation of apple juice; a related product, perry (also known as pear cider) is produced by the fermentation of pear juice.</string>
    <string name="sprite_description">Sprite tastes great with beer, tequila, whiskey, wine, cognac, and liqueurs, and you can enjoy different cocktails recipes. But the best of the best is the pairing of vodka and Sprite. The lemon-lime flavor of Sprite complements the spice and citrus notes of vodka.</string>
    <string name="seven_up_description">Despite their similarities, 7 Up and Sprite are two distinct drinks. 7 Up has a sweeter and more syrupy taste than Sprite, making it a better choice for those who enjoy a sweeter beverage. Sprite also has a more effervescent and citrusy flavor than 7 Up. There are so many different soda options out there, and so many of them are great to chase vodka with. Whether it\'s 7-Up, Sprite, Mist Twist, Sierra Mist, or some other lemon-lime soda, it will compliment the taste of vodka – especially any flavored vodka – and eliminate any burn that comes with the shot.</string>
    <string name="blackberry_brandy_description">Premium blackberries are blended with fine Brandy to create this delicious spirit, made specially to the Polish taste. Slightly higher in alcohol content than a typical flavored Brandy. Floral bouquet leads to a rich and smooth palate full of fresh fruit flavor with a baking spice background.</string>
    <string name="peppermint_schnapps_description">Peppermint schnapps is a distilled spirit made by adding peppermint flavoring to a clear grain spirit. It tastes like a liquid candy cane, with an astringent, almost mouthwash-like finish. Most sources believe the original version originated in Germany (in German the term Schnaps means a strong alcoholic beverage).</string>
    <string name="creme_de_cassis_description">Crème de cassis (French pronunciation: ​[kʁɛm də kasis]) (also known as Cassis liqueur) is a sweet, dark red liqueur made from blackcurrants. Crème de cassis bottled at 15% ABV. Several cocktails are made with crème de cassis, including the popular wine cocktail, kir.</string>
    <string name="type">Type: %1$s</string>
    <string name="category">Category: %1$s</string>
    <string name="glass">Glass: %1$s</string>
    <string name="instructions">Instructions: %1$s</string>
    <string name="ingredients">"Ingredients: "</string>
    <string name="drink_type_ingredient_detail">Drink type: %1$s</string>
    <string name="is_alcoholic">Alcohol: %1$s</string>
    <string name="coil_image_url_ingredients">https://www.thecocktaildb.com/images/ingredients/%1$s.png</string>


</resources>